Lal Bahadur Budha

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Contact

9865818795

☐ lalbahadurbc2054@gmail.com

Maitidevi - Kathmandu

https://github.com/stu9437l

Skills

- React JS / Next JS / React Native (basic)
- Node JS / Express JS / GraphQL (basic)
- Mongoose / MongoDB
- HTML-5
- Cascading Style Sheets (CSS3)
- Javascript / Jquery
- Figma

Educations

BE Computer

Pokhara University (2016 - 2021)

+ 2

NAST (2014 - 2016)

SLC

Jana Jagriti Higher Secondary School (2014)

Languages

- Nepali (Native)
- Hindi (Intermediate)
- English (Basic)

Certifications

- Web Designer (broadway infosys)
- React Developer (broadway infosys)
- PHP basic (Nast)
- Java basic (Nast)

Professional Summary

Enthusiastic Frontend developer focused on crafting great web experiences. Designing and coding have been my passion since the day I started working with computer but I found myself into Web Developer since 2021.

And Passionate of continuous leaning from the seniors and while still nurturing juniors developers. want to accomplish as a Fullstack developer if i get right opportunity in right place. Still seeking desire and challenging position in your company.

Experiences

Web Developer Internship

Neputertech Pvt. Ltd. (March 2021 - May 2021)

- First-hand experience in real web projects
- Opportunity to learn from senior designers and self-study
- An awesome period of skill development and growth

Junior Web Developer

Neputertech Pvt. Ltd. (2021 - 2022)

- Achieved financial independence through paid work
- Supported senior designers in web development tasks
- Gained knowledge in website development and interactive UI design
- Learned how to effectively communicate with clients and gather their requirements

Mid Level Web Developer

Neputertech Pvt. Ltd. (2023 - current)

- Currently working as a professional web developer
- Proficient in developing and managing web applications in any company
- Overcame initial complexity of web development through research, self-study and practice
- Continuously upgrading skills to become a full-stack developer
- Seeking the right opportunity to achieve future goals

Some Important Projects

- https://failure.gg
- https://sociospotech.com
- https://broadwayinfosys.com
- https://sojhai.com (new)
- https://satkar.com (new)
- MIS
- https://darmastore

Please check github link for more projects.